Menu

Table of content

### Legal and Privacy

#### Privacy Policy

#### Terms of Service - Individual

[Flat](https://flat.io/en/) > [Legal and privacy information](https://flat.io/en/policies/) > [Flat - Privacy Policy](https://flat.io/en/policies/privacy-policy/) > Privacy Policy - Annex 3 - Cookies

Language

🇺🇸

🇪🇸 Spanish🇫🇷 Français🇯🇵 日本語

Privacy Policy - Annex 3 - Cookies
==================================

_This is the Annex 3 of our [Privacy Policy](https://flat.io/en/policies/privacy-policy/)._

| Cookie name | Party setting cookie | When is the cookie set? | When does the cookie expire? | Type of cookie | Purpose of cookie |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
| `flat.sid` and `flat.did` | Flat | When you first access our website | Never | Strictly necessary | Session |
| `hl` | Flat | When you first access our website | Never | Strictly necessary | Language preference |
| `_pk_id` | Flat | When you first access our website | 13 months | Analytics | To distinguish users |
| `_pk_ref` | Flat | When you first access our website | 6 months | Analytics | To store referrer information |
| `_pk_ses` | Flat | When you first access our website | At the end of your browsing session. | Analytics | To store session information |
| `__stripe_mid` and `__stripe_sid` | Stripe | When you access a payment page | 1 year | Payments | Session |
| `_cioid` and `_cioanonid` | Peaberry Software Inc. DBA Customer.io | When you first access our website | 1 year | In-App communication | To store unique user identifer |

Can't find your answer?

Get in touch with our team. We’re here to help.

Copyright © 2024 Tutteo Limited
